We don't have the evidence to build a case.
Not for lack of trying.
Mon as grunts walked.
Who the hell were those guys anyway?
They were just his hired muscle.
We did learn something from Chenbin's wife, though.
She met him.
He'd stopped by with Chen Jin.
I remember.
He was here to see Bean.
I called Bean to see if he was coming home.
He said no, but that he'd call Chen Jin later.
They didn't stay long after that.
Last thing.
Is this the other man who was with Chen Jin?
That's him.
I'm sure.
I just assumed he worked for Chen Jin.
Oh, right.
He also moved the fruit to the kitchen before they left.
Oh, wait.
I was here the whole time he was in the kitchen.
Could he have planted the money?
But why frame Chenbin?
I don't understand.
What's going on?
Is Captain Chen involved in this?
Maybe.
Maybe not.
It's still early in the investigation.
I'm still trying to make sense of what happened.
So is that all you can remember?
Right now, we need as many details as possible.
No matter how small.
Yes, that was everything.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could be more help.
Hey, what do you know about Chen Jin?
Could it be him?
The one possessing people?
Sounds right.
He has the money to cover his tracks.
And his job is the perfect cover.
He can hide in plain sight.
It's not him.
It couldn't be.
Trust me, I wouldn't know.
We started at the academy at the same time, then joined the force together.
Out of the two of us, he was the better cop.
To this day, I've never met a more dedicated officer.
He and I had a lot of cases that ended with him injured or nearly dead.
Which wouldn't have happened if he had a power like yours.
Eventually, we were reassigned.
We got new partners, new cases, and naturally grew apart.
Until that day.
It's fine.
I'll drive.
Why don't you take a nap on the ride over to the crime scene?
I appreciate it.
A woman was killed in her apartment in the Xiaoxing neighborhood.
We think it was a burglary.
The woman happened to be home, and things went wrong from there.
Captain, are you alright?
Jin Jin!
I want all of you out of here right now!
You shouldn't have been there, but I'd just taken over the case.
I didn't know his wife was the victim until after I was on the scene.
Later on, we learned that she was pregnant when she died.
Only a few weeks.
What happened to the burglar?
Did you catch him?
Yes, we did.
But that wasn't the end of it.
There wasn't enough evidence to convict him.
So we managed to get away scot-free.
Then, about six months after his acquittal, he was found in his home, hanging from a noose.
Police found a suicide note in which he confessed to both the burglary and the murder.
Not everyone believed it.
Some even suspected that Chun Jin had killed him.
That's when he left the force and started up his law firm.
We didn't speak after that.
Now that I've seen what he's become, he feels like a stranger.
Tell me, have you found him yet?
You really are insane, you know that?
This plan is risky enough.
You're lucky that we still have a chance to pull this off, provided we remain one step ahead of the police.
We should find more people.
Just to be safe.
Right. Yes, sir.
Captain Xiao, is that all?
While I appreciate the update, I doubt that's why you came to see us.
Right. About that, I need your help.
Huh? With what?
We found this on the hospital's surveillance footage.
Who is that?
Let me see.
Lu Guang, this is right outside your room.
Who the hell is this, huh?
Hey, what are you hiding?
I know you know something.
It's all right.
You're safe.
Please, tell us what happened.
Nothing happened.
They just gave me this.
Who are they?
I honestly have no clue.
They didn't speak and they wore a mask, so I never saw their face.
Please!
As far as I can tell, it's just a photo.
The only unique things about it are the drawing and message on the back.
That's all I have.
The note in the drawing appear to be left by a child.
Might be the one in the photo, but we can't say.
It's said, can't lose my brother.
Maybe our mystery person wants us to find him for them?
Maybe.
Lu Guang, did you learn anything with your power?
No, nothing yet.
Maybe once I fully recovered.
Normally I have 12 hours to search.
But for now, I can't use my power that long.
Hey, I can do it.
I'll jump in and you guide me around like we always do.
I'd rather you not.
Too dangerous.
You can enter photos?
How's that work?
Well, it's essentially time travel.
Lu Guang sees the pass through photos,
while Chang Chaoshi possesses who takes them.
Time travel?
That's amazing.
No case would go unsolved.
It's not that easy.
You can do a lot of damage.
The world could come undone,
and you never know.
It's incredibly risky.
Hmm.
I hadn't thought of that.
The butterfly effect.
Can't imagine that kind of responsibility.
Not just that.
While the past can be changed,
you can't change everything.
What's done is done.
There's no point in fighting it.
But we have to.
Because the future is still ours to make.
You taught me that.
That photo may be the key to solving all of this.
That alone should make it worth the risk.
Besides, Captain Xiao needs help.
And this is something that only you two can do.
Hmm.
All right.
Just remember.
First, you get 12 hours.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing.
And third, past or future.
Must remain untouched.
I'll be damned.
So that's it?
He just disappears and now he's in the past?
See?
It prints the photo by itself.
Let's take a look.
Bring it here, please.
Kay.
Was that...
Honey, did you just answer me?
But...
Don't.
You're supposed to be mute.
Just keep your mouth shut from now on.
Fine.
Wait, this kid is mute?
That's a good start, but we're gonna need more.
Look around you.
What's there?
Find something.
Anything that can tell you where you are.
Hey, calm down.
What are you hearing right now?
Just let them work.
Remember, they're the experts.
They'll get you what you need.
Don't worry.
Come on.
Lu Guang?
Say something for me.
What should I do now?
I know you can do it.
Xiaxiu, please, try again.
Don't cry, sweetie.
It's alright.
I pushed you hard.
Hey, I'm sorry, honey.
I won't do it anymore.
It's probably for the best that you take a break for the time being.
We'll find the secret behind the photo, but it's gonna take a while.
Right.
I'm sorry.
This is all new to me.
Let's shift focus, then.
I could use your help, actually.
Do you have any idea why I was the one possessed?
That answer is obvious.
We know the killer's power needs photos.
So they got one of you.
The question is where they found it.
Um, I don't have a lot online.
My parents kept photo albums, but those are all physical.
They're not exactly tech savvy, so doubt it was them.
It doesn't have to be a picture of you, per se.
It could be a group shot.
Oh, Shishan-shan?
But any photo with me would be on her phone.
Which Liu Min got a hold of.
While he was being controlled.
I'm calling her right now.
Hey, what's up?
Oh, did you hear about Liu Min?
You did.
So he really did it, then?
Well, but how?
Later, okay?
Right now, I need you to check your phone.
Do you have any pictures of me or ones where I'm in the background?
I think.
Hang on, I'll check.
I'm not seeing one yet.
Maybe one with the two of us together.
I thought I had one.
I took a selfie outside your studio, and you got caught in the background.
That's it.
Captain Xiao, can you check something else?
I want to know if that photo was sent to anyone recently,
especially if it was to someone you don't recognize.
It would have been on the night that Liu Min was arrested.
Yeah, I'm looking through my emails.
I haven't found anything.
Check your text, then.
It could have been sent that way.
Hey, Lu Guang.
Where is this lady taking me?
As soon as I'm packed, we can head out.
All right?
This feels sudden.
Is it because I slipped up earlier?
Doubt it.
I can still see where you're going.
That tells me that nothing significant was changed.
I'm not finding anything.
Why is this so important to Chaolang?
The killer could have altered your phone's text history.
Okay.
I'm sending her number to my people.
They can pull up her phone records.
Just wait, okay?
Today is your follow-up with Dr. Qin.
Be a good girl while he takes a look.
It's been a while since her last treatment.
How has she been doing since then?
Amazing.
Doctor, I heard her speak today.
I wish that you could have heard her.
That's wonderful.
Now that we know what works for her, we can tackle the problem head on.
This guy's a quack.
Hey, don't judge.
Everyone has their own beliefs, okay?
We don't have to agree or even understand.
Just respect it.
This is why I keep telling you you should read.
The more you know, the more you can empathize.
He's so damn pedantic.
Does he treat everyone like that?
Luke Long is emotionally mature for someone his age.
These meds don't even have side effects listed.
Now then, let's see that hand.
Hey, there's nothing to be scared of.
Once I check your pulse, I'll know the next step in your treatment.
This guy isn't going to notice me when he checks your pulse, right?
Really?
Now you believe in this stuff?
Hmm.
What is it?
Is there something wrong?
This will sound strange, but her pulse is rather masculine for a girl.
Almost as if she were a boy.
What does that mean, doctor?
Should I be worried?
Well, no.
It means the medicine is working.
Your daughter's pulse is getting stronger by the day.
That means stronger energy and stronger blood as well.
Did this guy really just say stronger blood?
Incredible.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you.
Dr. Chin really is a miracle worker like everyone says.
He helped me hear my little Shishi speak today.
We're on Dongmal Road.
There's a cyber cafe at the intersection.
And a Yongshin salon across the street.
Dongmal Road.
Cyber cafe.
Yongshin salon.
We know the address for the doctor.
And based on the description he gave us,
they're east of the Nande district right now.
We won't have anything specific until Cheng Xiaoshu finds a name and number for the neighborhood.
That's better than nothing.
We still don't know how any of this connects.
Oh, who this lost brother is.
Stop for a second.
Then help carry the medicine.
Huh?
Right now?
Yes.
The child noticed that her mother was struggling and wanted to help.
What is it, Shishi?
Oh, thank you.
But Mommy can handle it.
Don't.
My, my.
You're just full of surprises today, aren't you?
When did you get so strong?
Idiot.
Stop breaking character.
Get your head in the game.
If that girl wrote the known,
you'd think we'd have seen or heard about her brother by now, right?
And what does she or her mom have to do with Tianjin or Liu Min?
All we have is info, no context.
Hey, it's me.
Find anything?
What you did?
Do we know what was sent then?
It was that thorough.
Well, can you recover anything?
Yeah, I can wait.
Who does the number belong to?
Almost.
There.
Good job.
Oh, shoot.
We were so close.
Looks like we've got enough for one more try.
You ready?
I got this!
Stupid red piece of crap!
Hey, Shishi.
Look, I found more coins.
Let's try again.
Her name's Liu Lan.
She lived at 48 Tongli Lane in the Nandu district.
Almost.
There you go.
Come on.
You're right there.
That's it.
Weird thing is, records show she passed away a few years ago.
Huh?
Are you sure?
Why would the text from Xu Shanshan's phone go to the number of a dead woman?
Sir, I only know what the phone company sent.
I double-checked it.
This is some crazy shit.
Do we know anything about this Liu Lan?
Sir, you're going to have to wait on that.
We've got a situation down here.
Wait, what?
And they said they're a witness?
Yes.
They're claiming they've seen everything on all our open cases.
What else did they say?
All right, then.
Why don't you tell us everything from the beginning?
What?
They said they'd only speak to Cheng Xiaoshu.
Oh, for an evil so unspoken.